<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Krzysztof Dolega</title>
    <link>https://qualiaq.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Krzysztof Dolega</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2019 13:10:07 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://qualiaq.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why have a personal website?</title>
      <link>https://qualiaq.github.io/post/personal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2019 13:10:07 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://qualiaq.github.io/post/personal/</guid>
      <description>Hello World</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello</title>
      <link>https://qualiaq.github.io/post/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 13:10:07 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://qualiaq.github.io/post/hello/</guid>
      <description>Hello World</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Krzysztof Dolega</title>
      <link>https://qualiaq.github.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://qualiaq.github.io/cv/</guid>
      <description>Postdoctoral Fellow
Ruhr-Universität Bochum, Institut für Philosophie II Universitätsstr. 150 Bochum Germany 44801 Publications Edited Volumes  Smortchkova, J., Dolega, K. , &amp;amp; Schlicht, T. (forthcoming). Mental Representations: The Foundation of Cognitive Science. OUP: New York. Dolega, K., Roelofs, L. &amp;amp; Schlicht, T. (2018). Special Issue: Enactivism vs. Representationalism. Philosophical Explorations, 21(2).  Journal Articles  Dolega, K., Schlicht, T. &amp;amp; Dennett, D.C. (forthcoming) Explaining or redefining mindreading? Behavioral and Brain Sciences, Commentary on Veissière et al.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who am I?</title>
      <link>https://qualiaq.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://qualiaq.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I am currently a postdoc at the Ruhr-Universität Bochum and a member of Prof. Tobias Schlicht&amp;rsquo;s research group realizing the Volkswagen Foundation grant entitled &amp;lsquo;Situated Cognition: Perceiving the World and Other Minds&amp;rsquo;.
My doctoral research was also conducted at the Ruhr-Universität, where I was supervised by Prof. Schlicht and Prof. Daniel Dennett. In my dissertation I investigated the way in which the computational models developed within the framework of predictive processing constrain the space of possible mechanisms underlying perceptual experience and whether the framework can yield a new perspective on the nature of consciousness.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>