<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>untagged on Krzysztof Dolega</title>
    <link>https://qualiaq.github.io/tags/untagged/</link>
    <description>Recent content in untagged on Krzysztof Dolega</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 18:06:18 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://qualiaq.github.io/tags/untagged/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Also featured in...</title>
      <link>https://qualiaq.github.io/outreach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 18:06:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://qualiaq.github.io/outreach/</guid>
      <description> A very short talk I delivered at the Philosophy of Human Technology Relations Conference     I was privileged to deliver the opening talk of the second Mathematical Consciousness Science Webinar:     My early doctoral work has been featured on the blog of the iCog network for postgraduates and early-career researchers working in interdisciplinary cognitive science  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentations</title>
      <link>https://qualiaq.github.io/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 18:06:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://qualiaq.github.io/talks/</guid>
      <description>Invited Talks 2020:
 &amp;ldquo;Attending to the Illusion of Consciousness - BayesianFrugality and the Representation of Attention&amp;rdquo;. (co-authored with Joe Dewhurst). Mathematical Consciousness Science Webinar: https://seminar.math-consciousness.org  2019:
  “The Principle and the Pauper: Free-energy explanations in cognitive science&amp;quot;. Bayesians: Current Topics in Cognitive Science. Institut für Philosophie II, Ruhr-Universität Bochum, Germany.
  “Rich in its poverty - perceptual experience in light of predictive coding&amp;quot;. 2nd Bochum Early Career Researcher Workshop in Philosophy of Mind and of Cognitive Science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://qualiaq.github.io/papers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 18:06:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://qualiaq.github.io/papers/</guid>
      <description>Edited Volumes   Smortchkova, J., Dolega, K. &amp;amp; Schlicht, T. (2020). Mental Representations: The Foundation of Cognitive Science. OUP: New York.
  Dolega, K., Roelofs, L. &amp;amp; Schlicht, T. (2018). Special Issue: Enactivism vs. Representationalism. Philosophical Explorations, 21(2).
  Journal Articles   Dewhurst, J. &amp;amp; Dolega, K. (2020). Attending to the Illusion of Consciousness. Journal of Consciousness Studies, 27/5-6: 54-61.
  Dolega, K. &amp;amp; Dewhurst, J.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who am I?</title>
      <link>https://qualiaq.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 18:06:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://qualiaq.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I am currently a postdoc at the Ruhr-Universität Bochum and a member of Prof. Tobias Schlicht&amp;rsquo;s research group realizing the Volkswagen Foundation grant entitled &amp;lsquo;Situated Cognition: Perceiving the World and Other Minds&amp;rsquo;.
My doctoral research was also conducted at the Ruhr-Universität, where I was supervised by Tobias Schlicht and Daniel Dennett. In my dissertation I investigated the way in which the computational models developed within the framework of predictive processing constrain the space of possible mechanisms underlying perceptual experience and whether the framework can yield a new perspective on the nature of consciousness.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
