<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>untagged on Krzysztof Dolega</title>
    <link>https://qualiaq.github.io/tags/untagged/</link>
    <description>Recent content in untagged on Krzysztof Dolega</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 18:06:18 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://qualiaq.github.io/tags/untagged/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Also featured in...</title>
      <link>https://qualiaq.github.io/outreach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 18:06:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://qualiaq.github.io/outreach/</guid>
      <description> A very short talk I delivered at the Philosophy of Human Technology Relations Conference     I was privileged to deliver the opening talk of the second Mathematical Consciousness Science Webinar:     My early doctoral work has been featured on the blog of the iCog network for postgraduates and early-career researchers working in interdisciplinary cognitive science  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentations</title>
      <link>https://qualiaq.github.io/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 18:06:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://qualiaq.github.io/talks/</guid>
      <description>Invited Talks 2021:
 &amp;ldquo;Canonical Microcircuits for Predictive Coding and the Phenomenal Overflow Hypothesis.&amp;rdquo; Cognitive science and Neuroscience seminar series, Computational Neuroscience and Visual Perception Laboratory. Atatürk Rönesansını Devam Ettiren Üniversite, Istambul, Turkey.  2020:
 &amp;ldquo;Attending to the Illusion of Consciousness - BayesianFrugality and the Representation of Attention&amp;rdquo;. (co-authored with Joe Dewhurst). Mathematical Consciousness Science Webinar: https://seminar.math-consciousness.org  2019:
  “The Principle and the Pauper: Free-energy explanations in cognitive science&amp;quot;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://qualiaq.github.io/papers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 18:06:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://qualiaq.github.io/papers/</guid>
      <description>Edited Volumes   Smortchkova, J., Dolega, K. &amp;amp; Schlicht, T. (2020). Mental Representations: The Foundation of Cognitive Science. OUP: New York.
  Dolega, K., Roelofs, L. &amp;amp; Schlicht, T. (2018). Special Issue: Enactivism vs. Representationalism. Philosophical Explorations, 21(2).
  Journal Articles   Bruineberg J., Dolega K., Dewhurst J. and Baltieri, M. (forthcoming). The Emperor’s New Markov Blankets. Behavioral and Brain Sciences, 1-63. doi:10.1017/S0140525X21002351
  Schlicht, T.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
